http://www.novadevelopment.com/company/legal-privacy/index.html

Sign-up for special savings by email
View Cart
Print Creativity
Greeting Card Factory Deluxe 11Photo Explosion 5.0Photo Explosion 5.0 DeluxePrint Artist® 25 GoldPrint Artist® 25 PlatinumScrapbook Factory Deluxe 5.0
Digital Photography
InPixio Photo FocusInPixio Photo Focus ProfessionalInPixio Photo MaximizerInPixio Photo Maximizer ProfessionalinPixio Photo Studio 10 ProfessionalinPixio Photo Studio 10 StandardMorpheus Photo MorpherMorpheus Photo Morpher for MacPhoto Explosion Photo RecoveryPhoto Explosion 5.0Photo Explosion 5.0 DeluxeScrapbook Factory Deluxe 5.0
Home & Living
Virtual Architect Home & Landscape Platinum Suite 9.0Virtual Architect Home Design For MacVirtual Architect Instant Makeover 2.0Virtual Architect Kitchens & Baths 9.0Virtual Architect Professional Home Design 9.0Virtual Architect Professional Home Design For MacVirtual Architect Ultimate Home Design with Landscaping and Decks 9.0
Utilities
Drive Erase ProfessionalMarine Aquarium Deluxe 3.0 for WindowsMyInvoices & Estimates® Deluxe 10Photo Explosion Photo RecoveryWebEasy Professional 10
Privacy PolicyYour privacy is extremely important to us. To better protect your privacy, we are making this privacy policy available to you so you can learn about our online information practices and the way we collect and use your information.
How Your Information is Collected
Nova Development ("Nova," "our," "us" or "we") licenses access to our software, services and websites (the "Sites") (collectively, the "Services") to you ("you" or "your"), under our Terms of Use and any applicable End User License Agreement.
When you place an order on our website ("Sites") or by using our Services, or download, activate or register a product or Service with us, you will be prompted to provide (and we will collect) certain types of personally identifiable information, such as your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, financial information (such as your credit card number) and other unique information such as unique device identifiers, geo-location, user IDs and passwords, transaction information and product and service preferences. We also collect the e-mail addresses of customers who communicate with us via e-mail and those who provide their e-mail address when joining our mailing list. In addition, we collect personally identifiable information that is voluntarily provided to us by visitors to our Sites or who use our Services in connection with activities such as contest participations, survey information and member account registrations.
We may collect non-personally identifiable (anonymous) information from all visitors to our Sites and users of our Services, regardless of whether they place an order with us or download software, volunteer such information, communicate with us, join our mailing list or otherwise. We may use such information and aggregate it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Sites and Services, the number of visitors to each page of our Sites and Services, the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers, and how our users use and interact with the Sites and Services. We may share this non-identifiable and aggregate data with our affiliates, agents and business partners, or disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our Sites and Services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.
We may also collect information about you from commercially available sources. Such information may include your name, address, email address and demographic data. The information that we may collect from these sources may be used along with the information that we collect from you when you visit the Sites or use the Services.
Cookies and Other Information Gathering Tools
Like many sites, we use "cookies." Cookies are small text files that reside on your device and identify you as a unique user. Cookies allow us to, among other things, measure activity on our Sites and Services and to personalize your experience. For example, cookies enable us to remember your viewing preferences without requiring you to re-type a user name and password. Cookies also allow us to track your status or progress when ordering products from us. If you choose, you can set your browser to reject cookies or you can manually delete individual or all of the cookies on your device by following your browser's help file directions. However, if you reject or delete cookies you may have some trouble accessing and using some of the pages and features on our Sites or Services. We also use other common information gathering tools such as web beacons and embedded web links.
We may also make use of log files in order to track information such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), platform type and date/time stamps. The log files may also contain information we gather that can be used in trend analysis, administration of the site, and overall demography tracking; this information is gathered through the counting of clicks and not linked to personally identifiable information.
Children's Information: We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18 and we do not target our Sites or Services to children under the age of 18.
How We Use Your Information
We use your personally identifiable information to fulfill purchases that you make through our Sites or Services, for marketing purposes, to provide service and support, and to improve the quality and type of applications we make available via our products. We share the information with affiliates and other reputable organizations for service, support and marketing purposes.
If you provide us with your postal or e-mail address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information about products, services and upcoming events. We may share your information with select business partners so that they may offer products and services that we believe will be attractive to our customers and to those who have subscribed to our mailing list.
In addition, we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties in order to: (i) respond to the requests of police and governmental authorities, (ii) comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order, (iii) help prevent fraud or to enforce or protect our rights or (iv) protect the personal safety of our employees and third parties. We may also share your information with or transfer it to third parties for business reasons, such as in the context of the sale or merger of our company or business.
Aggregate, anonymous data collected is statistical in nature, and does not include personally identifiable information. This data may be used to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our Services.
When you provide us with your credit card information we may redirect that information to certain third parties only for the purpose of payment processing in accordance with their own privacy and security policies.
Third Party Ad Servers; Behavioral Advertising
We may participate in behavioral-based advertising and use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf on the Sites and Services. Such providers may collect information about your visits to our Sites and use of our Services. They may use information about your visits to this Sites and use of our Services to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by many major websites.
We also work with third parties to monitor certain pages of our Sites and Services for the purpose of reporting website traffic and other advertising statistics. These third parties may use cookies and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our Sites visitors and Service users.
Links to Third Party Websites: The Sites and Services may contain links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. We do not control those websites or make any representations or warranties about their use or the third party policies that govern such use. Any personal information that is obtained by third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of third-party websites.
Integrating Third Party Services within the Services: The Service may allow you to enable various online third party services to be directly integrated into your device. By enabling such third party services, you are allowing us to share log-in information and other relevant information with these service providers. However, please remember that the manner in which third party services use, store and disclose your information is governed solely by the policies of such third parties, and we shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any third party service that may be enabled within the Services.
Security: We maintain reasonable and appropriate security procedures, but we cannot guarantee that your information will be secure in every circumstance.
Notices: If we are required to provide you with notice of a particular event or incident, we will send you such notice by mail, email or telephone.
Notification of Changes: We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically return to this page.
Changing Your Information: If you believe that you have provided us with information that is incorrect or that needs to be updated you may contact us by using the "Submit Ticket" option on our Support Home Page or by calling us at (800) 395-6682.
Opt-Out / Unsubscribe from Email Marketing: You can access the Sites without providing any personally identifiable information. However, you may not be able to use certain features of the Sites or Services (such as registering, opening an account or making purchases) without providing personally available information. Please visit our Remove from Mailing List Page if you would like to discontinue receiving marketing-related e-mails and opt-out of certain uses of your personally identifiable information by Nova.
Other Terms and Conditions: Your access to and use of the Sites and Services is subject to the Terms of Use and any applicable End User License Agreement.
How to Contact Us: If you feel that we are not following our stated privacy policy, or to be removed from our mailing list, you may contact us by using the "Submit Ticket" option on our Support Home Page or by calling us at (800) 395-6682.
Effective Date: This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 1, 2014. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, effective immediately upon its posting. Please check this page of the Sites periodically or access this Privacy Policy through the Services. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.
Company  |
Support  |
Retail Locations  |  Terms of Use  |  Privacy Policy  |  Site Map  |  Supplier Code of Conduct
Copyright 2020 Nova Development. All rights reserved.
